indiabook.com 2014-11-23

# Indiabook - Disclaimer - Privacy Policy

| India Search  
---  
Search Options:  
  
---  
Search Keyword  

Browse Resources  
---  
| ****  
---|---  
| **»»Women World**  
  
| **»»Travel**  
| **»»Kids**  
| **»»Health**  
| **»»Dating**  
| **»»Matrimonials**  
| **»»Home Pages**  
| **»»Greetings**  
| **»»Web Master**  
| **»»Shopping**  
  
Ads   
  
| 

|    **IndiaBook Disclaimer and Privacy Policy**|   
---|---  

---  
  
MegriSoft, which owns the indiabook.com is responible for maintaining the privacy of its users.MegriSoft's information gathering and dissemination policy is common to all its sites and is disclosed below:   
The Contents of User Email Communications. indiabook.com, will not monitor the contents of User email communications unless a) required to do so by law; or b) in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to protect and defend indiabook.com's rights or property; or c) when necessary to protect the personal safety of Users or the public. indiabook.com will not disclose the contents of User email communications to any party unless required to do so by law. User email accounts are password protected and Users are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the passwords.   
Personally Identifiable Information - When visiting indiabook.com's or any Partner's web site and signing up for or using indiabook.com services through a web page hosted by us, you may choose to supply indiabook.com with information that identifies you personally. For end-users, this information may include your name and contact information, gender, age group, occupation and industry, and user-comments and opt-in preference; we intend to collect shipping and billing information, which may, in the future, include credit card numbers, and other payment types of information. We also intend to collect behavior patterns, which may include recording frequency of use of our services, which and when items were purchased, at which site and page, and other information related to behavior patterns. We collect prospect information, which may include name, and contact information of individual(s) you think would be interested in our services. For Partners, the information we collect may include your name and contact information, your site's category, your web site information (URL, visitors per day,description of services offered at web site), and user- comments.   
When Partners add our services to their web site, end-user information collected is stored in our database. Thus,our database has information collected on our site as well as on Partner sites. As stated in the Partner and End-User agreements, indiabook.com and it's partner's have access to the information specific to their site only;The Way We Use Information We use the information you provide about yourself or others to complete the transaction for which it is intended. This may include administering a service such as email, search, community, e-commerce, etc., completing an order, shipping a product, or contacting you if you have indicated your permission to do so. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission except to the extent that is necessary to administer the services we offer our Partners and end-users.   
When we receive subscribed email addresses or get messages posted on our support forum, we use the return email addresses to reply with the information requested. For subscribed email addresses, we will email with service announcements and updates as requested. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.   
For end-users, when supplying name and contact information, shipping information, prospect information, and user-comments to indiabook.com, we will use it to answer your questions, ship your products, or provide you with the requested services. When supplying name and contact information to watchmail.com you can indicate your preference if you would like to be contacted to receive information and updates about indiabook.com's.   
In addition, when indicating your age, gender, occupation and industry, and contact information, we will extract non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our web site and services, and to share the aggregate data with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our web site, or that Y number of men and Z number of women use a certain service. Indiabook.com services may also utilize personally identifiable end-user information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to end-users based on their demographic and behavioral information. Also, we may use this information to gather aggregate behavioral patterns such as frequency of use of our services, interests, types of items purchased, how many items purchased, etc., to administer and improve our services accordingly. 

**Registration Information**. The registration form for the indiabook.com requires certain contact information (like a User email address, address and zip code) and demographic information (like a User's gender, age, and occupation)("Registration Information"). indiabook.com provides Registration Information to the party with which it has partnered to provide the mail Service. Registration information is also used by indiabook.com as follows:   
a) Custom WebMail Experience, Advertising and Promotions. indiabook.com is advertising supported. indiabook.com uses Registration Information to tailor the webmail experience and advertising to the interests of individual Users, and to send Users promotional information from indiabook.com sponsors when requested by individual Users. indiabook.com provides Registration Information to certain companies for analysis, modeling and comparison to enable indiabook.com to display advertisements which are available and suitable for individual Users; for fulfilling promotions requested by Users; and for displaying advertisements not served directly by indiabook.com. All such companies are required to sign confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements prohibiting them from contacting Users directly; using Users Registration Information in any way other than specified by indiabook.com; and from disclosing User Registration Information to any party other than indiabook.com-approved parties providing other services to indiabook.com, which parties are also required to sign confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements.   
b) indiabook.com Communication. indiabook.com uses Registration Information to contact Users if necessary regarding User accounts or other User service issues; to send Users Hotdak.com newsletters containing information on indiabook.com developments, new features, and member benefits. Users may opt-out of receiving Hotdak.com newsletters and other promotions.   
c) Third-Party Promotions. indiabook.com provides Registration Information to third parties to enable them to send Users promotions when requested by Users. indiabook.com has no control over, and is not responsible for, the use of Registration Information provided to such third parties. Users are advised to refer to the privacy policies of the applicable third parties. Users may opt-out of third-party promotional programs which they have previously authorized. 

**What about Cookies?**   
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a Web site if you do so.   
In addition to directly providing information to indiabook.com, you might also provide Profile Information through chat sessions, e-mail exchanges or bulletin board use made available to you on other sites, including other MegriSoft sites. Chat sessions and bulletin board or newsgroup use is considered public and you are responsible for your actions in these areas. The Hotdak.com Privacy Statement does not cover this type of transfer of your Profile Information. You should always be careful when distributing your Profile Information in this manner. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures reasonably designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How to Contact Us**   
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, send us an email at [support@megrisoft.com](mailto:support@megrisoft.com)   
© 2006-2007 Megrisoft. All rights reserved. Terms of Service Privacy Statement
